get a room get a
room Craigslist is not only a great
place to have one night stands with
murderers but you can also find
apartments on it sometimes I'm going to
show you guys photos of an apartment for
250 points I want you to come up with a
better line to sell it than the real
tagline all right here's the first one
basement for rent females
[Applause]
[Laughter]
only yes said was ug one way in no way
out points horrible horrible
points next one 250 a month not an
actual real
bedroom is that a it's like a it's like
a promo shot for
hoarders uh yes Doug stuff not
included
bus wait this is crazy so it looks like
there's a a door up here and then you
just sort of fall onto this pile of
garbage that's what the garbage is there
for is to catch
you free box fan all right next one $200
a month it's out the road so must be
willing to drive it's in Hawaii yes
Megan the only bus you're legally
allowed to jerk off
[Laughter]
in wa
wow
the ghosts of children are friendly
right points to dark Benson for
that